<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel><title>Levi Searches</title><link>https://levisearches.github.io//index.html</link>
<description>A blog about anything that comes to my mind.</description><language>en</language>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 15:05:20 -0300</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 15:05:20 -0300</pubDate>
<atom:link href="https://levisearches.github.io//feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<item><title>
#M01: Expanding the concept of Rules for Life
</title><description><![CDATA[

<p>Our initial reaction to any rule is to reject it, since we have free will, even if it is good for us. We tend to think that rules restrict and oppress us when, in fact, the opposite is true. Without rules, we quickly become slaves to our passions; without rules that give us clear guidance on what to do or not, we end up declining more and more. Therefore, rules are not restrictive but liberating.</p>
<p>If we take all possible models of life from Greek literature, we will see that there is a limit that cannot be exceeded.</p>
<p>Poetic meter serves the same purpose. It restricts the number of syllables and verses a poet can create. This restriction does not diminish or oppress but provides the freedom for the author to create art. 'The sonnet is a prison without bars,' Vinícius de Moraes.</p>
<p>Outside of the possible types and meter is where anomalies arise. Only artists with great mastery of the art can venture outside the line, outside the type, outside the meter, without losing themselves.</p>

<p>If you liked this content, consider supporting me (lightning network): <a href="https://getalby.com/p/levisearches">levisearches@getalby.com</a></p>

<p>Tags: <a href='tag_texts.html'>texts</a>, <a href='tag_meditations.html'>meditations</a></p>
<!-- text end -->
]]></description><link>https://levisearches.github.io//m01-expanding-the-concept-of-rules-for-life.html</link>
<guid>https://levisearches.github.io//./m01-expanding-the-concept-of-rules-for-life.html</guid>
<dc:creator>Levi Searches</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 15:04:42 -0300</pubDate></item>
<item><title>
Other places where you can read my texts
</title><description><![CDATA[

<p>Hey! I'm here just to tell you that I'm also posting on the Midnight Club. If you don't know what the Midnight Club is, well, it is a small community of writers from all the places around the world. The texts that I'm going to publish there has a fiction touch. The first text was <a href="https://levisearches.github.io/what-ends-is-the-world-and-the-flesh.html">this one</a>.</p>
<p>I also post my texts on Instagram (even though I don't like it very much). But yeah, that's it for now. I hope you'll like it!</p>

<h3>Links:</h3>
<ul>
	<li><a href="https://midnight.pub/~peshto">Midnight Club</a></li>
	<li><a href="https://www.instagram.com/levisearches/">Instagram</a></li>
</ul>

<p>Tags: <a href='tag_warning.html'>warning</a></p>
<!-- text end -->
]]></description><link>https://levisearches.github.io//other-places-where-you-can-read-my-texts.html</link>
<guid>https://levisearches.github.io//./other-places-where-you-can-read-my-texts.html</guid>
<dc:creator>Levi Searches</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 11:14:24 -0300</pubDate></item>
<item><title>
Hello, there!
</title><description><![CDATA[

<p>Hello, my name is Levi. I decided to create this website because I like to write and I would like to share my writings with you. If you like it, consider making a little donation.</p>

<p>My bitcoin lightning wallet: <a href="https://getalby.com/p/levisearches">levisearches@getalby.com</a></p>

<p>Thank you for being here!</p>

<p>Tags: <a href='tag_warning.html'>warning</a></p>
<!-- text end -->
]]></description><link>https://levisearches.github.io//hello-there.html</link>
<guid>https://levisearches.github.io//./hello-there.html</guid>
<dc:creator>Levi Searches</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 10:56:59 -0300</pubDate></item>
<item><title>
What ends is the world and the flesh
</title><description><![CDATA[

<p><em>August 8, 2023</em></p>

<p>Most people live most of their lives - or all of it - enthralled in a constant litany, in a constant noise. Earthly noise. Noise of mundane, everyday, and immediate worries. As if life were to end in the next moment.</p>

<p>Most do not realize the <em>au-delà</em> of life. Life does not end today, nor tomorrow, nor in the next decade. Life never ends; what ends is the world.</p>

<p>What comes after a bill? Another bill? And another, and another, and so on, until the grave puts an end to it? Does life end with the next bite or the next coin, the next pleasure or the next pain? Life never ends; what ends is the world and the flesh.</p>

<p><em> ~Levi Searches</em></p>

<hr>
<p>Tags: <a href='tag_texts.html'>texts</a>, <a href='tag_meditations.html'>meditations</a></p>
]]></description><link>https://levisearches.github.io//what-ends-is-the-world-and-the-flesh.html</link>
<guid>https://levisearches.github.io//./what-ends-is-the-world-and-the-flesh.html</guid>
<dc:creator>Levi Searches</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 10:56:59 -0300</pubDate></item>
</channel></rss>
